freshupnow.com 2013-06-04

# Privacy Policy

Advertisement

Privacy Policy

  * At freshupnow.com, we are much concerned to our visitors privacy, We will never sell, exchange, or release any of visitor's individual personal information to a third party without permission. 
  * freshupnow.com does not violate the copyright laws. freshupnow.com does not have any data uploaded to its servers. All of our contents are from other authentic sources, Like Youtube, Dailymotion, Facebook or Youku. 
  * From time to time, we may conduct online surveys or polls to get the opinion of our visitors and keep in touch with them. We may ask users for contact information (like email addresses. We are responsible to keep our visitors data secure. 
  * We may share personally identifiable information with third parties when the person submitting the information authorises us to share it or we are required to by law. 
  * Like many sites, freshupnow.com uses cookies. Cookies are data files that are stored on your computer. They contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. 
  * We use cookies for the benefit of our users. Cookies let us know if we have repeat visitors (a strong indication of happy consumers) and if we are delivering a quality product to our consumers. We also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites. freshupnow.com does not use cookies to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as contest registration (where a cookie allows to you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time) and personalization features where a guest requests certain information 
  * freshupnow.com never uses cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. freshupnow.com does not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes. Essentially, it is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for other consumers who we think will like our site. Cookies are not programs that come onto a visitor's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the visitor that has no meaning outside the assigning site. If a visitor does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the visitor to deny or accept the cookie feature. 
  * freshupnow.com contains many links to other sites. freshupnow.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. freshupnow.com does not share any of the individual personal information you provide freshupnow.com with the sites to which freshupnow.com links, although freshupnow.com may share aggregate data with such sites (such as how many people use our site). This Includes other third party sites on the Internet for which freshupnow.com provides search services. Please check with those sites to determine their privacy policy. 

Send us any suggestions if you have, regarding the site.
